export const DATA_PRODUCTS = [
  {
    id: '0001',
    name: 'Cropped Stay Groovy off white',
    price: 10.9,
    gender: 'Famale',
    thumbnailFront: '0001.1.webp',
    thumbnailBack: '0001.2.webp',
    size: ['L', 'XL', 'XXL'],
    freeship: true
  },
  {
    id: '0002',
    name: 'Basic Cactus White T-shirt',
    price: 13.25,
    gender: 'Famale',
    thumbnailFront: '0002.1.webp',
    thumbnailBack: '0002.2.webp',
    size: ['L', 'ML'],
    freeship: true
  },
  {
    id: '0003',
    name: 'Skater Black Sweatshirt',
    price: 25.9,
    gender: 'Male',
    thumbnailFront: '0003.1.webp',
    thumbnailBack: '0003.2.webp',
    size: ['XL'],
    freeship: false
  },
  {
    id: '0004',
    name: 'Black Tule Oversized',
    price: 29.45,
    gender: 'Famale',
    thumbnailFront: '0004.1.webp',
    thumbnailBack: '0004.2.webp',
    size: ['M', 'ML'],
    freeship: true
  },
  {
    id: '0005',
    name: 'Black Batman T-shirt',
    price: 10.9,
    gender: 'Unisex',
    thumbnailFront: '0005.1.webp',
    thumbnailBack: '0005.2.webp',
    size: ['xs', 's'],
    freeship: true
  },
  {
    id: '0006',
    name: 'Blue T-Shirt',
    price: 9,
    gender: 'Male',
    thumbnailFront: '0006.1.webp',
    thumbnailBack: '0006.2.webp',
    size: ['L', 'XL'],
    freeship: false
  },
  {
    id: '0007',
    name: 'Loose Black T-shirt',
    price: 14,
    gender: 'Male',
    thumbnailFront: '0007.1.webp',
    thumbnailBack: '0007.2.webp',
    size: ['L', 'XL', 'XXL'],
    freeship: true
  },
  {
    id: '0008',
    name: 'Ringer Hall Pass',
    price: 10.9,
    gender: 'Famale',
    thumbnailFront: '0008.1.webp',
    thumbnailBack: '0008.2.webp',
    size: ['L', 'XL', 'XXL'],
    freeship: true
  },
  {
    id: '0009',
    name: 'Grey T-shirt',
    price: 14.9,
    gender: 'Male',
    thumbnailFront: '0009.1.webp',
    thumbnailBack: '0009.2.webp',
    size: ['L'],
    freeship: true
  },
  {
    id: '0010',
    name: 'Black T-shirt with white stripes',
    price: 26.7,
    gender: 'Famale',
    thumbnailFront: '0010.1.webp',
    thumbnailBack: '0010.2.webp',
    size: ['L'],
    freeship: true
  },
  {
    id: '0011',
    name: 'Turtles Ninja T-shirt',
    price: 16.5,
    gender: 'Male',
    thumbnailFront: '0011.1.webp',
    thumbnailBack: '0011.2.webp',
    size: ['L', 'XL'],
    freeship: false
  },
  {
    id: '0012',
    name: 'Slim black T-shirt',
    price: 49.9,
    gender: 'Unisex',
    thumbnailFront: '0012.1.webp',
    thumbnailBack: '0012.2.webp',
    size: ['XL', 'XXL', '3XL'],
    freeship: true
  },
  {
    id: '0013',
    name: 'Blue Sweatshirt',
    price: 22.5,
    gender: 'Unisex',
    thumbnailFront: '0013.1.webp',
    thumbnailBack: '0013.2.webp',
    size: ['s'],
    freeship: false
  },
  {
    id: '0014',
    name: 'White T-shirt Gucci',
    price: 18.7,
    gender: 'Famale',
    thumbnailFront: '0014.1.webp',
    thumbnailBack: '0014.2.webp',
    size: ['XL'],
    freeship: false
  },
  {
    id: '0015',
    name: 'Tropical Wine T-shirt',
    price: 134.9,
    gender: 'Male',
    thumbnailFront: '0015.1.webp',
    thumbnailBack: '0015.2.webp',
    size: ['L', 'XL'],
    freeship: true
  },
  {
    id: '0016',
    name: 'Marine Blue T-shirt',
    price: 39,
    gender: 'Unisex',
    thumbnailFront: '0016.1.webp',
    thumbnailBack: '0016.2.webp',
    size: ['L', 'XL'],
    freeship: true
  }
];
